<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m /rō-hɪt/</title>
    <link>https://rkaushik29.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m /rō-hɪt/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="https://rkaushik29.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>project pegasus</title>
      <link>https://rkaushik29.github.io/pegasus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:33:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rkaushik29.github.io/pegasus/</guid>
      <description>Pegasus is a web3 application that generates an NFT for each digitally verifiable task (or set of) that an individual completes, proving the value they have added to the world.
problem descriptor Growing demand for jobs in companies that are growing, paired with a limited supply, leads to increasingly standardized testing processes in recruiting that are long, repetitive and generate no value.
the problem With agencies like Randstad and LinkedIn connecting people to enterprises without extensively verifying their expertise and experience, the hiring processes are gradually inching towards verifing skills of candidates in an extremely standardized fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>text</title>
      <link>https://rkaushik29.github.io/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 22:11:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rkaushik29.github.io/text/</guid>
      <description>Readings Currently Reading : 1984 Previously Read:
Title Author Fundraising Ryan Breslow The Return of the King J.R.R Tolkein The Two Towers J.R.R Tolkein The Fellowship of the Ring J.R.R. Tolkein Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX and the Quest for a Fantastic Future Ashlee Vance Atomic Habits James Clear Foundation&amp;rsquo;s Edge Isaac Asimov You can find a more detailed list of my readings on my Notion. or (an even more detailed list) on my Goodreads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>timeline</title>
      <link>https://rkaushik29.github.io/timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 01:35:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rkaushik29.github.io/timeline/</guid>
      <description>📄 Resume
2022 Software Engineering Intern @Staax , San Francisco CA Jun. 2022 - Present
Implemented an end-to-end user feedback system in the app, including a node.js API and a react native screen to supplement it. Developed an internal react webapp to display collected feedback. Engineered a data caching system with firestore and AWS-Elasticache for frequently accessed stock data, improving screen load time by 10x in the app. Created several AWS-CloudWatch queries and dashboards to retrieve user metrics like unique signups, and identify service errors in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>https://rkaushik29.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 17:36:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rkaushik29.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Finished products are for decadent minds.&amp;rdquo; - Bail Channis, Second Foundation
Hi 👋
I&amp;rsquo;m Rohit, a fourth year Computer Science undergrad at the University of Waterloo.
Originally, I come from Bangalore, India, informally known as the Silicon Valley of India, and rightly so in my opinion. I witnessed the growth of myriad small businesses1 (into large national and multi-national corporations) throughout my childhood, and thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;If they can do it, why not me?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
